Blake McCullough

Perth, WA
Blakeomccullough@protonmail.com.au
+61410468836

SUMMARY

I am a TAFE student working towards a career in the IT industry; specifically, Cyber Security or Programming. I have undertaken many roles over the last few years with most from directly approaching potential employers. These roles have provided me with a wide breadth of work experience, in particular the requirement of an employee for reliability and good customer service. I am interested in undertaken this role to further my vocational experience.

Website: https://blakemccullough.com/ GitHub: https://github.com/Blake-McCullough

EXPERIENCE

JayCar Joondalup

November 2021 -

Present

Sales Assistant

- Greeted customers with a friendly and helpful attitude.
- Answered any questions regarding inventory, sales, and promotions.
- Carefully and accurately rang up items and neatly packed customer bags.
- Worked well with other employees to ensure smooth processes.
- Focused on being punctual, hardworking, and reliable.
- Assisted with displays and offered ideas to increase product appeal.

HyprFire Perth

December 2021 -

January 2022

Internee

- Built package management system to store required packages for PacMan
- Built web scraper for getting directories and file names of an ftp server.
- Built system for automatically downloading necessary files and placing in correct

directories.

Red Rooster Joondalup

September 2020 -

January 2022

Front of house and back of house team member

- Process and fill customer food orders and prepare specialty dishes quickly and accurately.
- Operate cash register and credit card machine to process customer payments.
- Answer customer questions about food ingredients, freshness, and availability.
- Clean and straighten counters and tables at end of shift.
- Uphold commercial safety and sanitation standards.
- Operate high-volume cooking and assembly equipment.
- Measure and prepared raw food materials.
- Helped to order and stock received food supplies and equipment.

Cyber Saturdays

April 2021 -August2021

Mentor/Mentee

- Volunteer helping teach school children how to address cyber security challenges.
- Regular attendance at professional cyber security development activities.

Work Experience with ES2 Cyber Security

April 2021 -

November 2021

Cyber Security Consultant - Internee

- Perform Log review
- Write Risk Assessment
- Open-source intelligence gathering,
- Coding automation of activities.
- Perform Physical Pen Testing
- Peer reviewing of documents
- Programming

Beta Tester for GeForce Now

September 2021

User

- Provide accurate and detailed feedback to developers.
- Fill out bug reports correctly, including steps to recreate the bug.

Work experience with Microsoft

October 2021 --October 2021

Internee

- Provide customer service by greeting and assisting customers and responding to customer enquiries and complaints.
- Demonstrate the use or operation of merchandise.
- Describe merchandise and explain use, operation, and care of merchandise to customers.
- Entering, transcribing, recording, storing, or maintaining information in electronic form.

ViewTech3D

December 2020 -

April 2021

IT Assistance

- Commercial website development using WordPress software.
- Company file backup, management, and storage system implementation.
- Configuring servers to update hosted website.

Salmat Media Force Pty Ltd

July 2019 -

August 2020

Paper rounds delivery person

Retrieve assigned route papers from the main hub.

- Bundle assigned route papers for individual houses.
- Responsible for a delivery residential area.
- Reliably delivered newspapers in all weather.

MAJOR SIDE PROJECTS

- **Inactivity Identifier Bot** A Discord bot, designed to help identify users in a server who have not been active.
- Bot Server Count Bot -- A Discord bot, designed to display the amount of servers your discord bot is in.
- **Private Channels Bot --** A Discord bot, designed to create private text, and voice channels within a discord server.
- <u>Usage Alert system</u> -- A simple script used to send a webhook to your Discord server when you reach a certain limit of CPU usage
- YouTube to Text File A script/chrome plugin designed to get the current YouTube video you are watching, and pass it onto the text file, which can be read from OBS or other applications.
- Twitch speech video clip producer A script designed for streamers to use that will allow them automatically to create a 'clip' of there stream after saying any trigger words, such as 'clip that', this prevents them from having to go and manually make said 'clip'.
- VR Master League App Development An app for the VRML championships using an closed API with OAUTH2.0.
- Arduino USB media controller A project, using an Arduino Leonardo, and some bits
 and pieces, that allows me to control the volume of my computer, skip and rewind
 videos and mute.

EDUCATION

- 2015–2016: PEAC (Primary Extension and Challenge) in Primary School
- 2017: Was enrolled in the Academic Extension Program at Belridge Secondary Collage
- 2017: Participation award for Australian Mathematical Competition
- 2020: Competed in the WACTF and PECAN capture the flag challenge
- 20017-2021, Belridge Secondary College,
- 2022, Cert IV in Programming

SKILLS

- **Programming Languages:** C/C++, Godot, Visual basic, HTML, and Python, Latex, C#, Batch, Flutter, Dart.
- Operating Systems and Software: Linux, Mac OS, Windows 10, Windows 7, Windows XP,
 Office 365 software such as excel, Adobe software such as Photoshop, WordPress, and
 Cura.
- Microcomputers: Raspberry Pi's and Arduinos.
- Hardware: 3D printers, Desktops, Laptops.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Introduction to Cybersecurity by Cisco
- AHA Hospitality & Tourism Covid-19 Hygiene Course

PROFESSIONAL REFERENCES

 Andy Bartle Chief Technology Officer ES2

Phone: 0449 985 169 Email: andy@es2.com.au

Dr Michelle Ellis
Outreach and Engagement Coordinator
School of Science
Edith Cowan University
Phone: 0402 201 808

Email: Michelle.Ellis@ecu.edu.au